[
  {
    "id": "T1D01",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "With which countries are FCC-licensed amateur radio stations prohibited from exchanging communications?",
    "answers": [
      "Any country whose administration has notified the International Telecommunication Union (ITU) that it objects to such communications",
      "Any country whose administration has notified the American Radio Relay League (ARRL) that it objects to such communications",
      "Any country banned from such communications by the International Amateur Radio Union (IARU)",
      "Any country banned from making such communications by the American Radio Relay League (ARRL)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1D02",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Under which of the following circumstances are one-way transmissions by an amateur station prohibited?",
    "answers": [
      "In all circumstances",
      "Broadcasting",
      "International Morse Code Practice",
      "Telecommand or transmissions of telemetry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1D03",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "When is it permissible to transmit messages encoded to obscure their meaning?",
    "answers": [
      "Only during contests",
      "Only when transmitting certain approved digital codes",
      "Only when transmitting control commands to space stations or radio control craft",
      "Never"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1D04",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Under what conditions is an amateur station authorized to transmit music using a phone emission?",
    "answers": [
      "When incidental to an authorized retransmission of manned spacecraft communications",
      "When the music produces no spurious emissions",
      "When transmissions are limited to less than three minutes per hour",
      "When the music is transmitted above 1280 MHz"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1D05",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "When may amateur radio operators use their stations to notify other amateurs of the availability of equipment for sale or trade?",
    "answers": [
      "Never",
      "When the equipment is not the personal property of either the station licensee, or the control operator, or their close relatives",
      "When no profit is made on the sale",
      "When selling amateur radio equipment and not on a regular basis"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1D06",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What, if any, are the restrictions concerning transmission of language that may be considered indecent or obscene?",
    "answers": [
      "The FCC maintains a list of words that are not permitted to be used on amateur frequencies",
      "Any such language is prohibited",
      "The ITU maintains a list of words that are not permitted to be used on amateur frequencies",
      "There is no such prohibition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1D07",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What types of amateur stations can automatically retransmit the signals of other amateur stations?",
    "answers": [
      "Auxiliary, beacon, or Earth stations",
      "Earth, repeater, or space stations",
      "Beacon, repeater, or space stations",
      "Repeater, auxiliary, or space stations"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1D08",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "In which of the following circumstances may the control operator of an amateur station receive compensation for operating that station?",
    "answers": [
      "When the communication is related to the sale of amateur equipment by the control operator's employer",
      "When the communication is incidental to classroom instruction at an educational institution",
      "When the communication is made to obtain emergency information for a local broadcast station",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1D09",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "When may amateur stations transmit information in support of broadcasting, program production, or news gathering, assuming no other means is available?",
    "answers": [
      "When such communications are directly related to the immediate safety of human life or protection of property",
      "When broadcasting communications to or from the space shuttle",
      "Where noncommercial programming is gathered and supplied exclusively to the National Public Radio network",
      "Never"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1D10",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "How does the FCC define broadcasting for the Amateur Radio Service?",
    "answers": [
      "Two-way transmissions by amateur stations",
      "Any transmission made by the licensed station",
      "Transmission of messages directed only to amateur operators",
      "Transmissions intended for reception by the general public"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T1D11",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "When may an amateur station transmit without identifying on the air?",
    "answers": [
      "When the transmissions are of a brief nature to make station adjustments",
      "When the transmissions are unmodulated",
      "When the transmitted power level is below 1 watt",
      "When transmitting signals to control model craft"
    ]
  }
]